{
  "lectoratest": {
    "survey": "0",
    "grade": "1",
    "showresults": "20",
    "scoreonly": "0",
    "get": "0",
    "incvar": "0",
    "promptsuccess": "1",
    "persist": "0",
    "name": "Assessment",
    "subject": "Test Results",
    "testtime": "0",
    "numrandom": "0",
    "passinggrade": "80",
    "cancelfail": "a001_assessment_results_failed.html",
    "passdone": "a001_assessment_results_passed.html",
    "prevpage": "a001_assessment_results_begin_assessment.html",
    "gdocs": "0",
    "email": "0",
    "section": [
      {
        "index": "0",
        "id": "8231",
        "numrandom": "7",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "0",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "8456",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0021",
              "text": "Target housing addressed by the RRP Rule is a home or residential unit built before 1978, with some exceptions.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "1",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9086",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0032",
              "text": "Exceptions to the definition of target housing covered by the RRP Rule includes 1-bedroom and 0-bedroom dwellings as well as housing designated for the elderly.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "2",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "8474",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0022",
              "text": "Which of the following criteria is correct regarding a “Child-Occupied Facility” as defined by the RRP Rule?",
              "correctans": "sDq1p9v0q2q5v0qCqFq3q1p4q5q4v0q9qEv0q1v0p0p5q2qCq9q3v0qFp2v0q3qFqDqDq5p2q3q9q1qCv0q2p5q9qCq4q9qEq7v0p3p5q3q8v0q1p3v0q1v0p3q3q8qFqFqCv0qFp2v0q4q1p9q3q1p2q5v0q3q5qEp4q5p2",
              "choices": "Building is pre-1960|May be located in a public or commercial building such as a school or daycare center|Visited regularly by same child less than 3 years old|Visits are at least 4 days per week",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "3",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9105",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0033",
              "text": "Which of the following criteria is NOT correct regarding a “Child-Occupied Facility” as defined by the RRP Rule?",
              "correctans": "r6q9p3q9p4q5q4v0p2q5q7p5qCq1p2qCp9v0q2p9v0p3q1qDq5v0q3q8q9qCq4v0qCq5p3p3v0p4q8q1qEv0t3",
              "choices": "May be located in a public building such as a school|Visited regularly by same child less than 3|Visits are at least two different days per week|Combined weekly visits are at least 6 hours",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "4",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_3_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9125",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-3_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0034",
              "text": "Which of the following situations requires that the RRP Rule be followed?",
              "correctans": "s9qEp4q5p2q9qFp2v0p7qFp2qBv0q4q9p3p4p5p2q2q9qEq7v0q7p2q5q1p4q5p2v0p4q8q1qEv0t6v0q6p4t2v0qFq6v0p3p5p2q6q1q3q5v0q3qFqEp4q1q9qEq9qEq7v0qCq5q1q4vDq2q1p3q5q4v0p0q1q9qEp4v0q9qEv0q1v0p2qFqFqD",
              "choices": "A lead inspection showed no lead present in the home|An exterior job disturbing less than 20 ft2 of paint on a side of a house|Work done for free|Interior work disturbing greater than 6 ft2 of surface containing lead-based paint in a room",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "5",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_3_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9139",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-3_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0035",
              "text": "Which of the following situations requires that the RRP Rule be followed?",
              "correctans": "s1qEv0q5p8p4q5p2q9qFp2v0qAqFq2v0q4q9p3p4p5p2q2q9qEq7v0q7p2q5q1p4q5p2v0p4q8q1qEv0t2t0v0q6p4t2v0q9vEq5vEvCv0qFq6v0p3p5p2q6q1q3q5v0q3qFqEp4q1q9qEq9qEq7v0qCq5q1q4vDq2q1p3q5q4v0p0q1q9qEp4v0qFqEv0q1v0p3q9q4q5v0qFq6v0q1v0q8qFp5p3q5",
              "choices": "An exterior job disturbing greater than 20 ft2 i.e., of surface containing lead-based paint on a side of a house|An emergency renovation|No lead present in components being worked on |Minor repair or maintenance activities ",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "6",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_5_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9189",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-5_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0038",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of a Certified Firm?",
              "correctans": "s8q1p6q5v0q1qCqCv0q5qDp0qCqFp9q5q5p3v0p4p2q1q9qEq5q4v0q1p3v0s3q5p2p4q9q6q9q5q4v0r2q5qEqFp6q1p4qFp2p3",
              "choices": "Ensure all recordkeeping requirements are being met for each job |Ensure that work is conducted following practices specified in the Rule|Ensure that all renovation personnel are trained in lead-safe work practices|Have all employees trained as Certified Renovators",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "7",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_5_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9207",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-5_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0039",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of a Certified Firm?",
              "correctans": "s9qEq6qFp2qDv0s5r0s1v0qFq6v0q1qCqCv0qAqFq2p3v0q3qFqEq4p5q3p4q5q4v0p5qEq4q5p2v0r2r2r0v0r2p5qCq5",
              "choices": "Keep all records of pre-renovation education documentation|Assign a Certified Renovator to each job|Inform EPA of all jobs conducted under RRP Rule|Obtain and maintain firm certification",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "8",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_6_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9225",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-6_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0040",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of a Certified Renovator?",
              "correctans": "r2q5qDq1q9qEv0qFqEp3q9p4q5v0q4p5p2q9qEq7v0q1qCqCv0p3p4q1q7q5p3v0qFq6v0p2q5qEqFp6q1p4q9qFqEv0qAqFq2v0q9qEq3qCp5q4q9qEq7v0p3q5p4p5p0vCv0p7qFp2qBvCv0q1qEq4v0q3qCq5q1qEq9qEq7",
              "choices": "Train non-certified workers in lead-safe work practices |Remain onsite during all stages of renovation job including setup, work, and cleaning|Maintain copies of current training certificates onsite|Use EPA-recognized test kits to identify lead-based paint",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "9",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_6_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9243",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-6_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0041",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a responsibility of a Certified Renovator?",
              "correctans": "sFp6q5p2p3q5q5v0p4p2q1q9qEq5q4v0p7qFp2qBq5p2p3v0q9qDp0qCq5qDq5qEp4q9qEq7v0q3qCq5q1qEq9qEq7v0p6q5p2q9q6q9q3q1p4q9qFqEv0p0p2qFq3q5q4p5p2q5",
              "choices": "Oversee trained workers implementing cleaning verification procedure|Remain onsite during sign posting, work area preparation, and clean up|Ensure containment is maintained to prevent spread of dust and debris|Perform work and direct work of non-certified renovators",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "10",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_7_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9351",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-7_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0048",
              "text": "Which of the following is a requirement of the Pre-Renovation Education (PRE) rule?",
              "correctans": "s3q5p2p4q9q6q9q5q4v0p2q5qEqFp6q1p4q9qFqEv0q6q9p2qDp3v0qDp5p3p4v0q4q9p3p4p2q9q2p5p4q5v0p4q8q5v0r2q5qEqFp6q1p4q5v0r2q9q7q8p4v0p0q1qDp0q8qCq5p4v0p4qFv0p4q8q5v0qFp7qEq5p2v0qFq6v0p0p2q5vDt1t9t7t8v0q8qFqDq5p3v0q2q5q9qEq7v0p2q5qEqFp6q1p4q5q4",
              "choices": "Renovation workers must be educated regarding lead-safe work practices|Renovation firms must obtain certification from EPA |Training providers must become certified to teach the Initial Renovator training course|Certified renovation firms must distribute the Renovate Right pamphlet to the owner of pre-1978 homes being renovated",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "11",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_7_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9369",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-7_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0049",
              "text": "Which of the following statements is NOT correct regarding distribution of the Renovate Right pamphlet under the Pre-Renovation Education (PRE) rule?",
              "correctans": "r7q8q5qEv0p7qFp2qBq9qEq7v0q9qEv0p2q5qEp4q1qCv0p5qEq9p4p3vCv0p4q8q5v0p0q1qDp0q8qCq5p4v0q4qFq5p3v0qEqFp4v0qEq5q5q4v0p4qFv0q2q5v0q7q9p6q5qEv0p4qFv0p4q8q5v0p4q5qEq1qEp4p3",
              "choices": "When working in rental units, the pamphlet does not need to be given to the tenants|The pamphlet must be distributed not more than 60 days prior to beginning a renovation|Acknowledgement of receipt must be obtained at least 7 days prior to beginning a renovation |Let parents or guardians of children using a child-occupied facility know about the renovation and how to get a copy of the pamphlet",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "12",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_8_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9321",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-8_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0046",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT an area of difference between the RRP Rule and HUD’s Lead-Safe Housing Rule?",
              "correctans": "r5p3q5v0qFq6v0p0qFp7q5p2v0p3q1qEq4q5p2p3v0p7q9p4q8qFp5p4v0s8s5r0s1v0q1p4p4q1q3q8qDq5qEp4",
              "choices": "Clearance testing following renovation work|De minimis levels (amount of paint that has to be disturbed before rule is in effect)|Use of power sanders without HEPA attachment|Use of dry scraping to remove paint",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "13",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_1_1_8_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9335",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "1-8_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0047",
              "text": "“De minimis” levels under HUD’s Lead Safe Housing Rule are smaller than those in the RRP Rule, i.e., a smaller area affected by work requires following of lead-safe work practices in the rule.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "14",
        "id": "8357",
        "numrandom": "2",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "14",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_2_2_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9447",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "2-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0054",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a type of testing that can determine if lead is present in paint?",
              "correctans": "r6q9p3p5q1qCv0q9qEp3p0q5q3p4q9qFqEv0qFq6v0p0q1q9qEp4",
              "choices": "Paint chip sampling and testing |EPA-recognized test kit |X-Ray Fluorescence|Visual inspection of paint",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "15",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_2_2_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9465",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "2-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0055",
              "text": "Certified Renovators must use a lead test kit as well as collect a paint chip sample for lead analysis to determine the presence of lead-based paint prior to the start of renovation activities.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "16",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_2_2_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9479",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "2-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0056",
              "text": "After testing for lead-based paint, a Certified Firm does not have to report the results to the client.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "17",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_2_2_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9497",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "2-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0057",
              "text": "When paint chip samples are obtained by a Certified Renovator, the Certified Firm must provide a report to the client within ____days after completion of the renovation.",
              "correctans": "t3t0",
              "choices": "7|60|90|30",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "18",
        "id": "9348",
        "numrandom": "3",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "18",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_3_3_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9553",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "3-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0060",
              "text": "Which of the following are interior containment requirements of the RRP Rule?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "Close windows and doors in the work area|Close and seal HVAC vents|Use disposable tack pad at edge of plastic|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "19",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_3_3_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9567",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "3-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0061",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT an interior containment requirement of the RRP Rule?",
              "correctans": "sBq5q5p0v0q6qFqFq4v0q9qEv0p7qFp2qBv0q1p2q5q1v0p4qFv0p2q5q4p5q3q5v0p4p2q1q3qBq9qEq7v0qFq6v0q4p5p3p4v0q6p2qFqDv0p7qFp2qBv0q1p2q5q1",
              "choices": "Keep food in work area to reduce tracking of dust from work area|Post a warning sign at entry to work area|Cover immovable objects with plastic|Cover floors at least 6 feet from work area",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "20",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_3_3_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9581",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "3-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0062",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a requirement for exterior containment?",
              "correctans": "r7qFp2qBv0q9qEv0p7q9qEq4p9v0q3qFqEq4q9p4q9qFqEp3v0p4qFv0q8q5qCp0v0q4q9p3p0q5p2p3q5v0q4p5p3p4v0q3p2q5q1p4q5q4",
              "choices": "Work in windy conditions to help disperse dust created|Close all windows and doors within 20 feet of the work area|Cover the ground with plastic at least 10 feet from work area|Cover access doors in work area with two layers of plastic",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "21",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_3_3_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9599",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "3-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0063",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT an extra precaution to take to prevent spread of dust during exterior work?",
              "correctans": "s4qFv0qEqFp4v0q3qFp6q5p2v0q7p2q1p3p3v0p7q9p4q8v0p0qCq1p3p4q9q3v0p3qFv0p4q8q1p4v0q4p5p3p4v0q3q1qEv0p3q5p4p4qCq5v0q9qEv0q7p2qFp5qEq4",
              "choices": "Use vertical containment in windy conditions |Extend area of ground covered if working on second story |Use vertical containment when adjacent properties are close to work area|Do not cover grass with plastic so that dust can settle in ground",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "22",
        "id": "9514",
        "numrandom": "5",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "22",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9615",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0064",
              "text": "Which one of the following practices for removing lead-based paint is NOT prohibited under the RRP rule?",
              "correctans": "r3q1qEq4q9qEq7v0q2p9v0q8q1qEq4",
              "choices": "Open-flame burning|Heat gun above 1,100° F|Sanding by hand|Abrasive blasting without the use of HEPA vacuum attachments",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "23",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9633",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0065",
              "text": "Heat gun removal above 1,100° F, open flame burning, and torching for removal of lead-based paint are prohibited because they produce lead contaminated dust particulates which can be ingested into the lungs and left behind in a work area.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "24",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9647",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0066",
              "text": "When transporting waste from the renovation work area it must be contained to prevent the release of dust and debris.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "25",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9661",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0067",
              "text": "When cleaning the work site workers must maintain a completely spotless site in order to control the level of dust and debris.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "26",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_3_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9707",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-3_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0070",
              "text": "It is NOT necessary for workers to wear a respirator as long as they are wearing other protective gear such as coveralls and hat.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "27",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_3_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9721",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-3_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0071",
              "text": "Personal protection must be worn at all times including the planning, testing, and setup phases of the work.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "28",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_4_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9769",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-4_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0074",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT a characteristic of effective cleanup?",
              "correctans": "s3qCq5q1qEv0q6qCqFqFp2p3v0q9qEv0p7qFp2qBv0p2qFqFqDv0q2q5q6qFp2q5v0q3qCq5q1qEq9qEq7v0qFp4q8q5p2v0p3p5p2q6q1q3q5p3v0q9qEv0p2qFqFqD",
              "choices": "Clean top to bottom, from top of wall to window to floor|Clean all surfaces|Clean floors in work room before cleaning other surfaces in room|Keep dust from spreading to areas that were already cleaned",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "29",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_4_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9787",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-4_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0075",
              "text": "Clean floors of the work area first so that dust is NOT tracked around while cleaning other areas.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "30",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_5_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9735",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-5_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0072",
              "text": "When leaving the containment area which of the following actions should be taken to prevent the spread of lead-contaminated dust?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "HEPA vacuum shoes|HEPA vacuum and remove disposable coveralls and shoe covers|Wash hands and face|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "31",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_4_4_5_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9753",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "4-5_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0073",
              "text": "If leaving the work site for only a few minutes, there is no need to take steps to prevent the spread of lead-contaminated dust such as removing shoe covers and disposable coveralls.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "32",
        "id": "9612",
        "numrandom": "6",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "32",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9801",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0076",
              "text": "Paint chips and debris should be sealed in heavy-duty plastic bags.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "33",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9815",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0077",
              "text": "When doing interior cleaning, the floor should be cleaned first.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "34",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9833",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0078",
              "text": "In checking clean-up work, special attention should be paid to which of the following?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "Window sills|Bare Soil|Children’s Play areas|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "35",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9847",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0079",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT an acceptable practice for exterior clean-up?",
              "correctans": "s4p2p9v0p2q1qBq5v0q1qEq4v0p3q8qFp6q5qCv0",
              "choices": "Dry rake and shovel |Mist sheeting|Dispose of protective sheeting as waste|Inspect the plastic after cleaning for dust and debris",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "36",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_3_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9861",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-3_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0080",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT true during the cleaning verification process?",
              "correctans": "r4q8q5v0q6q9p2p3p4v0q3qCqFp4q8p3v0p5p3q5q4v0p3q8qFp5qCq4v0q2q5v0q4p2p9",
              "choices": "After wiping a designated area, the cloth should be lighter in color than the cleaning verification card|After wiping a designated area, if the cloth is darker in color than the cleaning verification card, the area needs further cleaning|The first cloths used should be dry|The cloth should be disposable",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "37",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_3_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9875",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-3_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0081",
              "text": "Surfaces to be tested during the Cleaning Verification include which of the following?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "Window Sills|Countertops|Floors|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "38",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_4_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18668",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-4_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0017",
              "text": "The Visual Inspection procedure can be conducted by a trained non-certified renovator.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "39",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_4_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18686",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-4_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0018",
              "text": "Which of the following is NOT part of the Visual Inspection procedure?  ",
              "correctans": "s9q4q5qEp4q9q6p9v0p6q9p3q9q2qCq5v0p0q1q9qEp4v0q3q8q9p0p3v0qFqEv0q6qCqFqFp2p3v0qFqEqCp9v0",
              "choices": "Work from the area farthest from the entry back to the entry|It must be performed by a Certified Renovator|Ensure there is adequate lighting|Identify visible paint chips on floors only ",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "40",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_5_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9893",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-5_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0082",
              "text": "Dust clearance testing is required by HUD in many pre-1978 properties receiving Federal housing assistance.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "41",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_5_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9911",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-5_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0083",
              "text": "If post-work clearance testing fails, the renovation firm must re-clean the work area until dust standards comply with applicable state, territorial, tribal, and local standards.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "42",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_6_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9925",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-6_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0084",
              "text": "At the conclusion of a renovation, waste that has been collected from renovation activities must be stored under containment, in an enclosure, or behind a barrier that prevents release of dust and debris out of the work area.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "43",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_5_5_6_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9939",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "5-6_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0085",
              "text": "Which of the following is an example of hazardous waste that may be generated at a worksite?",
              "correctans": "r6q1q3p5p5qDv0q4q5q2p2q9p3",
              "choices": "Protective sheeting|Solid components with no peeling paint|Vacuum debris|Rugs & Carpets",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "44",
        "id": "9766",
        "numrandom": "3",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "44",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9959",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0086",
              "text": "Renovation records must be maintained for 3 years following completion of a renovation.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "45",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9977",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0087",
              "text": "The EPA may request records for renovations for up to ______ following completion of a renovation.",
              "correctans": "t3v0p9q5q1p2p3",
              "choices": "30 days|6 months|3 years|7 years",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "46",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "9995",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0088",
              "text": "Which of the following documents must be maintained ONSITE during performance of a job?",
              "correctans": "s1v0q3qFp0p9v0qFq6v0q1v0s3q5p2p4q9q6q9q5q4v0r2q5qEqFp6q1p4qFp2v0s9qEq9p4q9q1qCv0p4p2q1q9qEq9qEq7v0q3q5p2p4q9q6q9q3q1p4q5v0q1qEq4v0q1v0q3qFp0p9v0qFq6v0q1v0s3q5p2p4q9q6q9q5q4v0r2q5qEqFp6q1p4qFp2v0r2q5q6p2q5p3q8q5p2v0p4p2q1q9qEq9qEq7v0q3q5p2p4q9q6q9q3q1p4q5",
              "choices": "Paint testing results|Copy of Certified Renovator Initial training certificate|Copy of Certified Renovator Refresher training certificate|A copy of a Certified Renovator Initial training certificate and a copy of a Certified Renovator Refresher training certificate",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "47",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10009",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0089",
              "text": "Which documentation must be maintained ONSITE for each job?",
              "correctans": "s3qFp0p9v0qFq6v0s6q9p2qDv0s3q5p2p4q9q6q9q3q1p4q9qFqEv0",
              "choices": "Copy of Firm Certification |Receipts for lead-safe renovation materials|Proof of owner-occupant pre-renovation education|None of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "48",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_3_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18764",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-3_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0101",
              "text": "If dust clearance sampling is performed in lieu of a clearance verification, a copy of the dust sampling report must be provided within 30 days of renovation completion to the person who contracted for the renovation.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "49",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_3_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18782",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-3_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0102",
              "text": "If an EPA-recognized test kit is used to test surfaces, the firm must submit a report within 30 days with which of the following?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "Make and model of EPA test kit|Description and location |Results of the test|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "50",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_4_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18800",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-4_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0103",
              "text": "The Post-Renovation report serves to document all aspects of lead-safe work practices by the Certified Renovator and other workers onsite while working on a particular renovation.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "51",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_6_6_4_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18818",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "6-4_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0104",
              "text": "The Post-Renovation report should include which of the following?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "Documentation of training for Certified and non-certified renovators|A description of work area and waste containment|Proof of successful cleaning verification|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "index": "52",
        "id": "9956",
        "numrandom": "4",
        "page": [
          {
            "index": "52",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_1_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10050",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-1_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0091",
              "text": "If Certified Renovator is NOT onsite, availability via telephone is acceptable. ",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "53",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_1_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10068",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-1_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0092",
              "text": "Training of non-certified renovators can take place in which of the following ways?",
              "correctans": "s1qCqCv0qFq6v0p4q8q5v0q1q2qFp6q5",
              "choices": "On the Job|Classroom with hands-on practice|Provided by a third party who is also a Certified Renovator|All of the above",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "54",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_2_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10086",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-2_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0093",
              "text": "Which of the following activities can a trained non-certified renovation worker do?",
              "correctans": "r7q5q1p2v0p0q5p2p3qFqEq1qCv0p0p2qFp4q5q3p4q9p6q5v0q5p1p5q9p0qDq5qEp4",
              "choices": "Post warning signs without supervision|Cleaning Verification|Determine if lead-based paint is present|Wear personal protective equipment",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "55",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_2_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10100",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-2_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0094",
              "text": "The trained non-certified renovator can do all of the following except:",
              "correctans": "s4q5p4q5p2qDq9qEq5v0q9q6v0qCq5q1q4vDq2q1p3q5q4v0p0q1q9qEp4v0q9p3v0p0p2q5p3q5qEp4",
              "choices": "Determine if lead-based paint is present|Wear personal protective equipment such as safety goggles and shoe covers|Keep the work area clean to prevent the spread of dust|Dispose of waste water with a waste disposal company",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "56",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_3_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10114",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-3_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0095",
              "text": "Which of the following documents is the primary resource that a Certified Renovator should use to train non-certified renovators?",
              "correctans": "r3p4q5p0p3v0p4qFv0sCs5s1s4v0r3s1s6s5v0r2q5qEqFp6q1p4q9qFqEvCv0r2q5p0q1q9p2vCv0q1qEq4v0r0q1q9qEp4q9qEq7",
              "choices": "US Department of Housing and Urban Development guidelines|State and Local regulations|Small Entity compliance Guide to Renovate Right|Steps to LEAD SAFE Renovation, Repair, and Painting",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "57",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_3_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10132",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-3_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0096",
              "text": "The Renovate Right pamphlet is the best guide for Certified Renovators to train non-certified renovators.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "58",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_4_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10146",
              "type": "2",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-4_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0097",
              "text": "Which of the following activities does not contribute to Step 4: Control the Spread of Dust?",
              "correctans": "s1p6qFq9q4v0q2qCqFq3qBq9qEq7v0p4q8q5v0p7qFp2qBv0p2qFqFqDv0q4qFqFp2v0p3qFv0q4p5p3p4v0q4qFq5p3v0qEqFp4v0q3qFqEq3q5qEp4p2q1p4q5v0q9qEv0qFqEq5v0p2qFqFqD",
              "choices": "Avoid blocking the work room door so dust does not concentrate in one room|Vacuum suits when exiting work area|Use tack pads to keep shoes clean |Wrap components securely when removing ",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "59",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_4_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10164",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-4_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0098",
              "text": "A trained non-certified renovation worker is responsible for at least 4 of the 7 steps to lead-safe practices including: protect self, control spread dust, leave work area clean, and control waste.",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "60",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_5_eq1.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "10178",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-5_EQ1",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0099",
              "text": "The RRP rule requires that documentation on training non-certified workers be maintained including which worker has which training, a list of all training topics covered for each worker, and a signature of the Certified Renovator who did the training.\\r",
              "correctans": "r4p2p5q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          },
          {
            "index": "61",
            "name": "a001_assessment_chapter_7_7_5_eq2.html",
            "question": {
              "id": "18865",
              "type": "1",
              "weight": "1",
              "name": "7-5_EQ2",
              "var": "VarQuestion_0105",
              "text": "After the job is complete, documentation of training for the trained non-certified renovation worker can be thrown away.",
              "correctans": "s6q1qCp3q5",
              "choices": "True|False",
              "allowmult": "0",
              "persist": "0",
              "gradeindividual": "0",
              "surveyquestion": "0",
              "anyanswer": "0",
              "casesensitive": "0",
              "separator": "|",
              "relationship": "0"
            }
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}
